{
    "target_configs": {
        "player": {
            "name": [
                "player_1_8KLBC9",
                "player_5_8KLBC9",
                "player_3_8KLBC9"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                1,
                5,
                3
            ],
            "animation": [
                "crouch",
                "liedown",
                "in_vehicle"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "A man wearing sunglasses, dark green long-sleeve shirt, light cargo pants, black gloves, and brown boots",
                "A female soldier wearing green tactical uniform, backpack, and black boots. Hair is tied back. She carries a utility vest and accessories.",
                "A woman with medium skin, dark hair in a bun, wearing a dark V-neck shirt, light pants, and brown boots"
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    13788.049,
                    2639.569,
                    -12713.082,
                    0,
                    156.2288794889741,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    13690.457,
                    2662.965,
                    -12713.082,
                    0,
                    113.89176526544418,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    14186.93,
                    2837.094,
                    -12712.922,
                    0.0,
                    0.0,
                    0.0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "None",
                "None",
                "None"
            ]
        },
        "car": {
            "name": [
                "car_0_8KLBC9",
                "car_3_8KLBC9"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                0,
                3
            ],
            "animation": [
                "None",
                "None"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "Grey car, compact, four-door, SUV style, modern structure",
                "Yellow vehicle with black stripes, modern style, compact structure"
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    14111.091,
                    2666.005,
                    -12712.971,
                    0,
                    -38.667909130700096,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    13123.108,
                    2619.037,
                    -12712.968,
                    0,
                    53.33656856282491,
                    0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "BP_Hatchback_child_base_C",
                "BP_Sedan_child_extras_C"
            ]
        }
    },
    "sample_configs": {
        "sample_center": [
            13816.583,
            3156.718,
            -12713.024
        ],
        "sample_radius": 1077.5012458805973
    },
    "refer_agents_category": [
        "player",
        "car"
    ],
    "safe_start": [
        [
            13538.54,
            3186.453,
            -12713.024,
            0,
            -72.47829456882423,
            0
        ],
        [
            13142.969,
            2289.815,
            -12706.451,
            0,
            37.125401000998025,
            0
        ],
        [
            14587.478,
            2151.529,
            -12710.51,
            0,
            148.34292887423067,
            0
        ]
    ],
    "Questions": {
        "relative_distance": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses, the_woman_in_camo_vest or the_woman_in_deep_V_top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_camo_vest",
                    "B. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_camo_vest"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_camo_vest, the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses or Grey_SUV?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses",
                    "B. Grey_SUV"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_deep_V_top, Grey_SUV or the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. Grey_SUV",
                    "B. the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses"
                ],
                "answer": "A. Grey_SUV"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Which is closer to Yellow_Car, the_woman_in_camo_vest or the_woman_in_deep_V_top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_camo_vest",
                    "B. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_camo_vest"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses, Yellow_Car or Grey_SUV?",
                "options": [
                    "A. Yellow_Car",
                    "B. Grey_SUV"
                ],
                "answer": "B. Grey_SUV"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_camo_vest, Yellow_Car or the_woman_in_deep_V_top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. Yellow_Car",
                    "B. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
                ],
                "answer": "B. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Which is closer to Grey_SUV, Yellow_Car or the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. Yellow_Car",
                    "B. the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses"
                ],
                "answer": "B. the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses"
            }
        },
        "counting": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "How many humans are in a crouch position in the scene?",
                "answer": "A. one"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "How many individuals are lying prone in the scene?",
                "answer": "A. one"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "what is the total number of distinct humans?",
                "answer": "A. three"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Among all the described human figures, how many are men?",
                "answer": "A. one"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "How many women are present among the detailed human figures?",
                "answer": "A. two"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "How many of the human characters are wearing glasses?",
                "answer": "A. one"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Excluding those wearing glasses, how many human figures are there?",
                "answer": "A. two"
            }
        },
        "state": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "What is the state of the man wearing sunglasses and light cargo pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. standing",
                    "B. crouch",
                    "C. lying down",
                    "D. running"
                ],
                "answer": "B. crouch"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "What is the state of the woman in the camo vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. standing",
                    "B. sitting",
                    "C. liedown",
                    "D. walking"
                ],
                "answer": "C. liedown"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "What is the state of the woman with the dark V-neck shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. in a car",
                    "B. standing",
                    "C. sitting",
                    "D. walking outside"
                ],
                "answer": "A. in a car"
            }
        },
        "relative_location": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in camo vest relative to the man in light pants and sunglasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the right of",
                    "D. To the left of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the right of"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in deep V top relative to the man in light pants and sunglasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. Behind",
                    "B. To the left of",
                    "C. In front of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. In front of"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Where is the Grey SUV relative to the man in light pants and sunglasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the back-right of",
                    "D. Slightly above"
                ],
                "answer": "A. In front of"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Where is the man in light pants and sunglasses relative to the woman in deep V top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-right of",
                    "B. Directly behind",
                    "C. To the back-left of",
                    "D. To the front-left of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the back-left of"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Where is the Yellow Car relative to the Grey SUV?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. To the front-right of",
                    "C. To the back-left of",
                    "D. Directly above"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the back-left of"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Where is the Grey SUV relative to the Yellow Car?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-left of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the back-right of",
                    "D. Directly below"
                ],
                "answer": "A. To the front-left of"
            }
        }
    }
}